Emre Özkan

+90 536 071 96 99 • emreozkan2000@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/emre-ozkan-ce • Antalya, Turkey

SUMMARY

I graduated from Antalya Bilim University with a scholarship in Computer Engineering (English). My interest in technology led me to this field. I had some experiences in web, mobile development and information technologies. I focused more on WEB, IOS development and interface design.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

March 2024 - Present Receptionist

Ruin Adalia Hotel

Working as a receptionist at the Ruin Adalia Hotel in Antalya Kaleiçi.

Software Engineer September 2023 - February 2024

Celadonsoft

Software Engineer at Celadonsoft. HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, Postgresql

Software Engineer Intern August 2023 - September 2023

Celadonsoft

Software Engieneering Internship at Celadonsoft. HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, Postgresql

June 2023 - February 2023 SAN Tourism Software Group

Internship as a Mobile Developer at SAN Tourism Software Group. Worked with the mobile team and experienced and assisted them mostly on IOS development and API usage.

IT Intern July 2022 - August 2022

Antalya Bilim University

Mobile Development Intern

Information Technologies Internship at Antalya Bilim University. I gained experience with the IT team in areas such as the university's network, servers and cyber security.

IT Intern August 2021 – September 2021

Selectum Luxury Resort

Information Technologies Internship at Selectum Luxury Resort Hotel in Antalya Belek. I worked on the hotel's servers, network connections, MySql etc.

EDUCATION

BSc. Degree In Computer Engineering

Antalya Bilim University

September 2019 - June 2023

SKILLS

Web and IOS Development

• Data Management

• HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

UI/UX Design

• Version Control with Git and Bitbucket • PHP, Laravel, Postgresql, MySQL

• Team Leadership

Communication

· Swift, Java

ADDITIONAL INFORMATIONS

• Languages: English C1, German A2

Licenses: Class B Driver's License (EU)

Certificates: IOS Programming with Swift, Web Development with HTML5, Javascript Fundamentals